EL GHALIDI WALID

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+34 623 95 69 77

walidelghalidi2001@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/walidelgld/

https://github.com/Nightmarle



About Me

I'm a 22-year-old with a background in Computer Science from ULB, I've now become a Junior Software Developer with a passion for efficient software solutions. I'm dedicated to ongoing collaborative learning and staying current with industry trends. Excited to contribute to dynamic development projects.

Expertise Skills

- MicroServices
 - Spring Framework
 - Maven Gradle
 - Express JS
 - React
 - SQL/NOSQL
 - Adaptability
 - Leadership Teamwork

Education

- 09/2020 06/2022
 - Université Libre de Bruxelles Computer Sciences

Languages

• English: C1

• French: C1

• Spanish: A2

Work Experiences

Internship

11/2023 - 01/2024

Revamped website functionality, improved app efficiency, collaborated on backend; adaptive problem-solver.

Software Developer Bootcamp

BeCode: 05/2023 - Now

- News App
- Chat App
- Football Statistic App
- Stock Viewer App
- LokkerRoom App

Student Jobs

11/2020 - 05/2022

- Supervisor of Study Hall
- Robotics Coach for children
- Football Coach